<resources>
    <string name="app_name">San Francisco Tour Guide</string>

    <string name="category_attraction">Attraction</string>
    <string name="category_activities">Activities</string>
    <string name="category_food">Food</string>
    <string name="category_nightlife">Nightlife</string>

    <string name="goldengate_info">Pedestrians including wheelchair users and bicyclists can go on the sidewalks of the bridge during daylight hours but roller blades, skateboards and roller skates are not permitted. There are vista points on both north and south sides of the bridge with parking lots.</string>
    <string name="alcatraz_info">Alcatraz Cruises is the official ferry provider to Alcatraz and back. Departures start at 9:30 AM and are available every half an hour throughout the day. However, please note that these cruises frequently sell out, so as much as possible, plan and book your cruise in advance, especially in the summer and on holidays. To purchase tickets, view the schedule and/or for more information, visit the Alcatraz Cruises web site at www.alcatrazcruises.com. Touring the island will be at your own pace. There is no formal tour but an audio tour is available for the cell house portion of your visit. This award winning audio tour is available in many languages including English, Spanish, Japanese, French, Italian, German, Dutch and Mandarin and can be purchased upon your arrival on the island or with your ferry ticket. Evening tours of Alcatraz are also available. Visit the Alcatraz Cruises web site for additional information. The weather on Alcatraz varies every day on the island, sometimes even on the same day. It can be warm, windy and wet any day of the year. The best way to prepare yourself is to dress in layers and wear comfortable shoes as well.</string>
    <string name="pier_info">Pier 39 is a shopping center and popular tourist attraction built on a pier in San Francisco, California. At Pier 39, there are shops, restaurants, a video arcade, street performances, the Aquarium of the Bay, virtual 3D rides, and views of California sea lions hauled out on docks on Pier 39's marina. A two-story carousel is one of the pier's more dominant features, although it is not directly visible from the street and sits towards the end of the pier. The family-oriented entertainment and presence of marine mammals make this a popular tourist location for families with kids. The pier is located at the edge of the Fisherman's Wharf district and is close to North Beach, Chinatown, and the Embarcadero. The area is easily accessible with the historic F Market streetcars.</string>
    <string name="coit_info">Advance elevator ride tickets to view spectacular 360 degree city views and reservations for guided docent led tours of the Tower murals are available on site or through Plan Your Trip.</string>

    <string name="deyoung_info">Located in San Francisco's Golden Gate Park, the de Young showcases American art from the 17th through 21st centuries, modern and contemporary art, photography, international textiles and costumes, and art from Africa, Oceania, and the Americas. The ninth-floor Observation Level of the de Young's Hamon Tower offers breathtaking 360-degree views of San Francisco and the Pacific Ocean. Open Tuesday-Sunday 930am-515pm, Fridays (March-November) until 845pm, Closed most Mondays and holidays. General admission tickets start at $15 for adults and discounts are available for seniors and students. Youth ages 17 and under are free. Free general admission the first Tuesday of the month. Special exhibition tickets available for additional price. Prices, hours and programs are subject to change. Please visit deyoungmuseum.org for detailed listing of current and upcoming special exhibitions, events, and educational offerings.</string>
    <string name="attpark_info">ATT Park is the home of the 2010, 2012 and 2014 World Series Champion San Francisco Giants. Located on the city's scenic waterfront, the ballpark is a short walk from downtown San Francisco and Moscone Center and is accessible by every means of public transit. This classic urban ballpark features all of the amenities necessary to create a unique and memorable event, including restaurants, equipped for banquets and receptions and state-of-the-art meeting and conference facilities.</string>
    <string name="bigbus_info">Enjoy an open top double decker hop-on/hop-off tour, stopping at 20 major sites and attractions around the city, including crossing the Golden Gate Bridge. The loop is 2.5 hours if you stay on the bus for the entire duration of the tour. You have the option of listening to a live tour guide in English or recorded commentary offered in 10 different languages. Our starting point is at the Visitor Center in Fisherman's Wharf, however you can get on and off the bus at any of our stops around the city. Every evening, we have beautiful Panoramic Night Tours. 24 and 48 hour tickets are available. Big Bus can also accommodate private charters.</string>
    <string name="cruise_info">Add some inspiration to your next corporate event with Hornblower Cruises and Events. Plan an only-in-San Francisco experience complete with welcoming service, delicious cuisine and views of The Bay Area's most celebrated sites. Hornblower will help you plan the perfect cruise for an office party, team building activity, client entertaining event, or company holiday party. From food, to entertainment, to decor, we'll help you customize your package for an unforgettable cruise experience on the San Francisco Bay.</string>

    <string name="aster">Inventive, responsibly sourced Californian fare and extensive wines in a casual space.</string>
    <string name="shizen">Vegan fare, from faux-sushi and ramen to meatless small plates, in an inventive, wood-decked space.</string>
    <string name="rooh">Sophisticated bistro serving playful cocktails and modern Indian fare with California accents.</string>
    <string name="tratto">Tratto's flavorful menu of simple, delicious and shareable dishes coupled with casual, communal-style dining creates a neighborhood bar experience inspired by the Italian tradition of "aperitivo", or happy hour.Guests can enjoy playful twists on classic Italian cocktails, boozy Italian sodas, and beer and wine from California and Italy, including a jug of house wine from the taps.Choose from a wide selection of traditional small-plate antipasti, house-made pastas and pizzas, entrees served family-style, seasonal side dishes, and classic Italian desserts including ice creams, gelatos and sorbets.</string>

    <string name="bourbonbranch">Bourbon and Branch is a glimpse back on the 1920's, the era of Prohibition when alcohol was outlawed. You'll experience the ambiance of that time in an actual speakeasy that operated illegally at this location.</string>
    <string name="folsom">Famous DJs spin into the wee hours for packed crowds at this Friday and Saturday night dance club.</string>
    <string name="devilsacre">Join us for our special selection of cocktails, sodas and apothecary-inspired remedies in our Barbary Cost Era inspired bar.</string>
    <string name="temple">Chic, multiroom club with varied music and decor, plus an eco-conscious, interactive dance floor.</string>

</resources>
